Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- Series X. PHONOGRAPH RECORDS
  - Recording - I. M. I. - WFDR - [1950] (Box 250, Folder 8)
    Fari Employment Practices Commission, Discrimination; Lou Frankel; International Ladies Garment Workers - Delegates; recording - 16" record - one side, 33 1/3 rpm - time 15 minutes
  - Recording - WGY - Schenectady, N. Y. - Farm Forum - Cobleskill Bi-centennial - 7/25/52 - 1952 (Box 250, Folder 9)
    Cobleskill, N. Y. (Bi-Centennial); Agriculture; recordings (2) - 3 sides 12" - 78 rpm
  - Recording - Ike-Ike-Ike - [1952] (Box 250, Folder 10)
    U. S. Presidential Election (1952 campaign); recording - 10" record - 78 rpm - time 3 min. - piano, voice
  - Recording - ILO Presidency, acceptance speech - 6/5/53 - 1953 (Box 250, Folder 11)
    International Labor Organization; recording - 12 record, 33 1/3 rpm - both sides - time @ 15 min.
  - Recording - Rupert Baker - Speech - My Trip to Israel - 19-- (Box 250, Folder 12)
    Israel (trip to), speech in Omaha, Neb. - sponsored by Teamsters Union; recording - 12" record, 78 rpm
- Series XI. DRAWINGS/PLANS
  - [drawings/blueprints] Preliminary drawings of NYSSILR (4 blueprints) - 1946 (Map-case Folder 1)
    basement, 1st floor, 2nd floor, 3rd floor
- Series XII. CLIPPINGS
  - Newspaper clippings - 1947-1949, 1954 (Box 137)
    clippings mentioning I.M.I. from New York State newspapers, mostly Albany area, arranged chronologically
  - Newspaper clippings - 1949-1950 (Box 138)
    see description Box 137
  - Newspaper clippings - 1951-1952 (Box 139)
  - Newspaper clippings - 1954 (Box 140-141)
  - Newspaper clippings - 1954, 1956-1958 (Box 142)
  - Newspaper clipping scrapbooks: September 1953-December 1955 - 1953-1955 (Box 143)
  - Newspaper clipping scrapbooks: April-November 1948, January 1952-August 1953 - 1948-1953 (Box 144)
  - Newspaper clipping scrapbooks: June 1947-March 1948 - 1947-1948 (Box 145)
  - Newspaper clipping scrapbooks: November 1946-May 1947 - 1946-1947 (Box 146)
  - Newspaper clipping scrapbooks: May-October - 1946 (Box 147)
  - [U. S. Senate. LPW] Taft-Hartley Clippings - 1953 - 1953-1954 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate] S. J. Res. 1 - Printed material, clippings - 1953-1954 (Box 219, Folder 3-4)
    treaty making (constitutional amendment)
- Series XIII. MISCELLANY
  - Printing blocks (2) - 19-- (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - State Assembly Political Science Survey - 1937 (Box 173, Folder 40)
  - Automobile Depreciation - 1924-1927 (Box 247, Folder 32)